- Oh, great.
- Great.
(Leonard:)- Great.
(Leonard:)Well, bye.
(Leonard:)- Bye.
- Bye.
(Leonard:)Should we have invited her for lunch?
No. We're gonna start season two
of Battlestar Galactica.
(Leonard:)We already watched
the season two DVDs.
(Sheldon:)Not with commentary.
I think we should be good neighbors.
(Leonard:)Invite her over, make her feel welcome.
We never invited Louie/Louise over.
Well, and that was wrong of us.
(Leonard:)We need to widen our circle.
(Sheldon:)I have a very wide circle.
(Sheldon:)I have 212 friends on MySpace.
(Leonard:)Yes, and you've never met one of them.
(Sheldon:)That's the beauty of it.
I'm gonna invite her over.
(Leonard:)We'll have a nice meal and chat.
(Sheldon:)Chat? We don't chat,
at least not off-line.
(Leonard:)Well, it's not difficult.